a special human being,
but I don't want to be
a special human being.
I'm a light bulb, and I'm going
to be a little before you.
I'm going to be a little
bit more than the future.
I'm going to be a perfect world for this.
I'm going to live this way. Thank
you.
That thing is huge!
Wait, is that my goddess?
Your goddess?
Does that mean you used one
of your skills to summon her?
Fear me, you insignificant humans.
One of the twelve goddesses
stands before you.
I am the goddess of night.
I am so sorry. Were you sleeping?
When all the lands beyond the veil awaken,
this world shall be filled with darkness.
Specifically, my darkness.
I think she's basically saying
I'm sleepy leave me alone because
it isn't my time yet speech so
flowery She needs a translator.
Oh Raven dark servant of mine for what
reason have you manifested me this night?
Well,
it might be called a miracle
or maybe destiny or to
put it bluntly you might say
I called you by accident.
So I didn't really have a reason per
se to invite me unknowingly on a whim!
I must admit, such daring is truly
fitting for a servant of mine.
Interesting.
Is it just me, or do Schwarzie and
this goddess have the same vibe?
I already seem like they have a
better relationship than we do.
Schwarz von Liechtenstein-Lohengrom.
What is this?
I apologize for the
rudeness we've shown you.
I didn't think you were the real thing.
But I've been telling you
that this entire time!
You sad little wretched humans proposed
that my darkness-clad hero was false. Hm?
She's little now!
Whoa!
No, stop it!
I cannot fall under the
charm of some old guy!
Blasted!
I was taken completely unawares!
What is this?
Why does this somehow
feel like a violation?
Just as I thought.
Are you the hero of the Goddess of Love?
Oh, uh, yeah.
That's, uh, that's a thing that happened.
What?
So you're a hero as well?
My hero obviously has more
spirit and vigor than you.
I've won this.
I'm good with losing, but
could I have my clothes back?
But to summon two heroes at once, the
Goddess of Love has played a cunning hand.
Hey, yeah, you're right.
Why did Tachibana show up
here with another person?
Ah, well, my hero,
when you first had an audience with
me, I asked you something, yes?
The question was, what do you
believe to be the strongest of all?
The strongest what of all?
It's a raven dark blackness, a void of
pitch black slicing through everything!
A true blade of darkness!
That answer scores a perfect 100!
So that answer in turn gave birth
to this, the holy sword called Gram.
And it was so well made as if it
were the very embodiment of me.
I see.
This level of excitement is
what created that weapon.
No wonder it turned out like that.
How does it feel wielding my holy sword?
Oh, it's undergoing
maintenance right now, so...
I see.
Well, at least you're
taking good care of it.
That's great.
Don't worry, Schwartz.
If lying hurts your feelings, that
means there's still hope for your soul.
In this way,
the heroes we summon are subsequently
bestowed with our blessing,
as well as the abilities
and weapons they wish for.
That's the basic procedure
we have established.
Then does that mean...
If we ever get to see our goddess again,
then maybe I can get one of
those super powerful weapons too?
What should I choose?
The strongest of all, huh?
My mischievous inner child is
threatening to come out to play.
No, you've got it all wrong.
Going back to the question
of why the two of us
were summoned here together
I believe the answer
is that I am considered to be your
weapon Tachibana whoa you grasp things
quickly human child hold up a minute
no no this isn't right what isn't
right I mean this is ridiculous isn't
it seriously if it's true that means
you're the strongest of all not me
Tachibana I didn't know you thought of me
Put that smile off your face!
It's not happening!
I've never thought anything so
embarrassing in my entire life!
When I got summoned,
you probably just got caught up in it
because you were nearby, that's all!
It's too late to take it back, I'm afraid.
Crap.
Of course, at a time like this,
you bothered to counterattack.
Don't be embarrassed.
You're the one who's embarrassed!
Those two get along really well.
Audrey!
No, honored hero.
Will you marry me so we can be happy?
What are you doing, my lord?
There are two heroes gathered here.
If this is when the myths begin once
more, then I shall become your pipeline.
I'll be your bridge to
the world of politics.
Now I see.
I wondered why his lordship
hadn't gotten charmed by you,
but with the villagers,
it was religious belief.
Next was the jealousy of the elf.
Then it was the drive to
protect with the interrogator.
With his lordship, it's
his wish for success.
It seems likely that the
effect of your beauty
stirs different desires
in different people.
So in his case, your beauty, coupled with
your standing as hero, finally broke him.
I guess that makes sense.
But are you okay with that, Chinguji?
Because if that's true, then it means you've
been charmed by my most obvious aspect.
Hey, what's up, Chinguji?
You are so into me.
Am I not good enough for you?
With your beauty and
my knowledge combined,
we could control the
entire economy together.
You don't have to love me, but let's get
out there and save business and politics.
That's enough.
Stop, my lord.
Jinguchi.
Your actions will only
invite certain destruction.
Certain destruction.
So you mean to interfere.
To be clear, you two aren't
a couple or anything, right?
That's not what motivated
me to deliver that warning.
Hello, my lord.
If I may have your permission.
I mean, this is, after
all, medical treatment.
So this is the most efficient way to
remedy contamination of the psyche.
Hey, are we done?
I'm gonna go back home. Sure!
Thanks for everything!
So it's come to pass!
This spot where the goddess
descended is now Holy Land!
We shall embrace the night
and prosper as a town where
travelers can stop and rest
safely with no fear at all!
I guess in the end it was kinda good
that you called down the goddess.
I definitely wondered how
things would turn out at first.
Heroes!
I would like to ask for your
help in developing our town.
We can provide land, a place to
live, and funds, among other things!
What do you think?
Wait, do you mean that?
I wouldn't have to worry about
food or a place to sleep anymore?
I accept, by all means!
Ah, basically he'd be our patron.
And Miss Audrey, if you would also
consider staying on as a public symbol,
I can promise you three square
meals and a nap per day.
Oh wow, you've gone and offered me
exactly the kind of reward I would want.
That seriously calls to a
working adult's tired heart.
But I don't know, what
do you think, Jinguji?
I'm afraid I'm actually against it.
Why though?
Even if we don't do anything, we
get three square meals and a nap.
That's what everyone can tell dreams of.
I can't say I've ever dreamed of that.
And his lordship didn't say
we wouldn't have to work.
But he said I just have
to stay here. That's true.
All you have to do is stay and
entertain the important people.
Basically, you're a honey trap.
Sounds like you'll work at
night, so sure, take a nap.
It's still a trick.
But staying in one place is going
to be difficult for you right now.
Once people learn of your
presence, you'll be forced to flee.
People will hunt you
down to use or kill you.
Yeah, but if it means I get to go back
to who I was even a second sooner,
then I think I should make use of
whatever method might be available to me.
And besides,
if there's like some kind of dangerous
danger or whatever, you should protect me.
What if you get poisoned?
If we need a food taster,
we have schmarzzy!
Wait, why me?
Listen, all I know right now is that I
don't want to hike any more mountain paths!
Oh, I mean, your reasons
do seem legitimate.
His head's immersed in the
convenience of the modern era.
Look, Tachiobana,
I'm not opposed to strengthening
our pipeline to influential people.
We're certain to obtain a fair amount
of useful information if we stay here.
However, if we do stay, could we
still claim we're traveling freely?
We have earned a break.
We've been so busy with work and life.
When's the last time we took it easy?
Nobody's even watching us, so
why not kick back for once?
It isn't logical,
and I'm fully aware that there's an
obvious bias to my thoughts on this.
I assume that has something
to do with how much
I've enjoyed this sense
of being on vacation,
which is why I'm not ready
to accept this offer.
Jinguuji.
Well, what are your
thoughts on it, Tachibana?
Well, if you're gonna put it that way,
there's not much I can say, is there?
Okay, bye! Thanks for everything!
Thankfully, I was finally able
to obtain a map of this world.
It'll take two weeks to get
to the royal capital, right?
I don't wanna walk!
If we'd done exactly as that lord said,
he might have let us use
official transportation.
Hey, Jinguji, when we turned it down,
that emotional bias
you were talking about,
it's actually called being strong-willed.
I am not such a petty,
childish person as that.
Nope, you're right.
The truth is that you're more
childish than anyone ever.
You know I can't let that comment slide.
Hey, slow down.
I want you to explain
what you meant by that.
Okay, let's go to the royal capital.
Did you see what I saw?
Can we just decide to pretend we didn't?
I had a dream about when I was little.
In it, my vision was blurred with tears,
so I'm guessing it might not
have been a very good dream.
As I looked up at the sky,
I saw the light lance
down through the trees
and I remember the piercing
sound of the cicadas.
And there was this guy.
When was it when we first
started being friends?
Are you ready to go now, Tachibana?
Our elementary school composition book?
That brings back some memories.
Yeah,
I just had a super weird dream about back
when we were kids and
it made me remember it.
Take a look at this.
My dream was to turn into cellophane tape.
Yes, that's right, I had forgotten that.
It was so incomprehensible
it actually frightened me.
But if you were choosing between
this and becoming a woman,
I'd have preferred the cellophane tape.
Probably would have been less complicated.
Anyway, here, I want you to look at this.
What would you take with you to
be stranded on a desert island?
My name is written there.
Uh-huh, and now I get what I was thinking.
I didn't choose you because you
were the most powerful weapon.
I chose you because I
thought you'd be useful.
That was the theory.
Well, if that's what you want to
think, then I suppose it's fine.
I'm trying to clear up
your misunderstanding.
Right, sure, I get it, but unfortunately
we can't summon the goddess.
And there's no value debating
something we have no way of knowing.
Besides, that's a survey
from elementary school.
You still want to become cellophane tape?
Somehow, I highly doubt it.
And what do you know
about cellophane tape?
One thing I do know is that you
don't know anything about it either.
Don't be condescending to me!
Am I supposed to assume that you had a
way more brilliant dream as a kid then?
Stop!
Why would I do that?
Why do you think?
Because I'm embarrassed, of course!
So you really believe you
deserve to escape this
after openly making fun
of someone else's dream?
Put it down, you idiot! Wait, no!
What did you do to my book?
That's for being so stubborn.
You jerk!
Why won't you let me read it?
What do you expect after you
laughed at me back when I wrote it?
I did not.
All right, I know I went
a bit far crossing it out.
But you were being pretty
childish, too, weren't you?
I'm like, I care.
I'm gonna need a little
break from talking to you
Think about what you did
you do with an eggplant.
That's what you are An eggplant in a suit.
Eggplant.
Who the heck scribbles
over something like that?
What was jinguchi's dream anyway?
Shoot I wish I could remember.
My brain is just so
Huh?
Eggplant.
What's the deal with this town?
Why do they love squid so much?
My, what a lovely couple you are!
Care for some squid?
We're not a couple and
we don't need squid.
What, are you fighting right now?
That's quite a shame, I'm sorry!
But come on, it's squid!
Are you listening, young people?
When your heart is feeling prickly, that's
when you need to eat something tasty!
Go ahead, try our specialty in makeup.
Here, give it a try, young lady.
You know what?
Why not?
Thanks, my guy.
You know what grilled squid needs is beer.
Should I open up a can, I wonder?
Well, since the proprietor
is probably right,
will we just agree that we were both
being childish and leave it at that?
I know I went too far using that marker.
But since we're living together,
I would really appreciate it if you would
respect my privacy a little bit more.
Hey, it's not cool to ignore me, you know.
Are you listening, Tachibana? What the?
Where are you?
If this is a joke, it's
in really bad taste.
The squid shot guy is gone, too.
Could this be a kidnapping?
No, calm down, Jingle-ji.
You'll feel ridiculous if you're shaken
just because you can't see anyone.
We're talking about Tachibana here,
the kind of person who'd be
laughing and sneering at me.
from afar.
Some kind of payback for
what I did to the book.
If so, I think the best
thing I can do is to
show that I'm panicked.
If I pretend I've been
taken in by this, that
should be enough.
It's ridiculous, but giving mental
support is the right thing to do.
Tachibana doesn't even realize I'm the one
who has everything in the palm of my hand.
Of course, my wanting
to control this much is
definitely all about my own ego.
This squid is great.
And even Even if I don't fuss and
worry, Tachibana's a grown adult.
If it weren't for that effect on others,
none of this would even be a concern.
That cart...
It's the one the premiere was on.
I gotta say, that wasn't
a very enjoyable job.
But the pay was good, so I
just need to shake this off.
Huh? What?
What happened to my cart?
What's going on here?
So are you the owner of this vehicle?
I'm terribly sorry about that.
I only meant to take a little look around.
I didn't intend to destroy it, but...
my hands won't seem to stop shaking.
Okay, first, calm down.
I am completely calm, as
I believe you can see.
I'm actually incredibly calm.
In fact, you could say
that I am far too calm.
Would a calm person destroy a cart?
Here, take this.
It's an herb that people use to relax.
I will happily give it to
you for free. Smell it.
Are you a slave trader?
You had an elf woman on
this cart, did you not?
It's not my specialty,
but you can think of me as a trader
who deals in a wide variety of goods.
Why were you looking for that elf?
No, the person I'm looking for is
a blonde, blue-eyed young woman.
You have any idea where I might find her?
No, no, I don't deal in kidnapping.
Ah, but could it be that
she's very beautiful?
Sure.
And did she disappear in this town?
Yes.
Then it might be best for
you to hurry on your way!
I was just thinking that it's been a while
since I did a job like
this that I didn't enjoy.
And the elf I delivered
was really beautiful.
I didn't know they'd
use her as a sacrifice.
So what's your big plan,
bringing me to a place like this?
What are you planning to do?
I think you already know, don't you?
Is this really happening?
Has this all been leading to that?
He's a human male whose desires
are clear for anyone to see.
It would be even more strange if this
didn't lead to something like that.
Is this where my journey ends?
I'm sorry, subjects of my village.
But if I'm to be sullied,
I'd rather kill me!
If you plan to do as you
like with me, I'd rather die!
Oh, you will.
Well, you are a sacrifice, after all.
A what now?
You haven't heard?
Tonight, after the festival
ends, you'll be an offering.
Then I really am going
to die? That's right.
I feel bad for you.
Same here.
But it really would be
such a terrible waste.
That perfectly well-balanced figure.
and those eyes with such intelligence.
The fine skin and cheeks
and lips like roses.
Endlessly brimming with
mysterious elegance.
It's the first time in my life that
I've seen so beautiful a woman.
Huh?
How fascinating that there are
humans who understand my beauty.
So what you're saying is, you need me.
Because the offering must be beautiful?
Yes, very good, you've got that correct.
Our deity does require that
beautiful people be sacrificed.
And while there were a good
handful of other candidates,
you were unanimously chosen.
Wow, seriously?
It was unanimous that I should die?
Well, I suppose since I've been
chosen, there's nothing to be done.
I guess being too beautiful
really is a crime.
And this, this is the
punishment I'm receiving for it.
There's a strange heat to
the way this man looks at me.
And now that I look more closely, he
might give up a manly, handsome vibe.
I see.
This man must be in love with me.
If he is,
then I may have to use my allure to
manipulate him in order to make my escape.
What's allure, really?
How do I use it?
What do I need to project it?
Like this?
Or like this? What's going on?
She's making strange poses.
You just need to behave yourself
until you're sacrificed.
That girl there, the sacrifice?
I'm not so sure about that, Henry!
Meggie, why are you here?
What business are you about when
we already have our sacrifice?
You're absolutely right, we certainly do.
But what if there were a girl who is
even more beautiful than that one?
Where am I? What's going on?
It's you!
Let's go!
Let's go! Yeah! Fabulous! Fabulous!
Who are you?
You know man is like
yeah Fantasy And you can
go You can go You can
go Girl is like a saint
List Love is like a
black girl You can go Ah,
which can you Just for you I'll try it You
can go I will take you
I'll take you I'll take
Fantasy You can't I can't
this year's festival is upon
us and the squid will dance
all young and lively young
and lively and the sacrifice
is blinding young and lively
young and lively squid squid